addicting-arcade.com 2008-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Addicting Games

We appreciates our relationship with you, respects that your information is yours, and is committed to safeguarding your privacy when you're using our web site. The following describes our collection of and use of any information that we may collect from you.

**Questions**

If you have any questions, Please do not hesitate to [Contact Us](mailto:webmaster%20at%20addicting-arcade%20dot%20com). 

**Your Information**

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our web page. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our web page.

**We Use Cookies Only For Members**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable us to recognize your computer and to deliver personalized features. We use cookies to recognize your membership only and never share members' information with others.

**Our Third Party Advertisers Might Use Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We do not receive any such information from our third party advertisers nor do we have any control over such third party advertisers or the use of any such information that is collected.

**We May Amend This Privacy Policy**

If in the future this Privacy Policy is amended or updated, you will be subject to this Privacy Policy as amended or updated. We will not notify you of any amendments or updates to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy often for any changes hereto.
